Huan, how could it be Huan?
Hey, here it comes.
The assassins are all from the Royal Family. Mafena, Mafena, Mafena, Mafena. No, I mean Mafena. Mafena is a sitting duck.
Your Honor, he kidnapped a wealthy magistrate and brought disaster upon the people of the county.
It's from your Master Huang's family.
I was wondering why you wouldn't pay to suppress the bandits. So you're the thief crying 'Stop thief!'!
You're pointing a gun at me.
You want to kill me?
Do you see? This is what happens when you're a bandit. Even my own father would have to die. He died a worthy death.
Rebellion!
The bandit, Huan, was executed by Master Huang five times. He killed his own kin, silenced witnesses, and implicated this old woman.
To kill to silence the witness. So you're the leader of the bandits, Zhang Mazi.
If you're going to kill your own kin for the sake of justice, then fine.
You pay the money, I'll pay the tax. Great!
Three days later,
It must be given to the county magistrate.
A surprise.
Master Tang, he was Hu Wan's savior, and now he's your savior as well.
You, explain it to me.
What's a surprise?
Let me translate for you. What's a 'surprise'? Does that even need translating?
I asked you to translate for me. What do you mean by "you"?
Surprise! It's a surprise, no need to translate. Don't tell me you don't get what 'surprise' means. I'm telling you to translate 'surprise' for me! Translate 'surprise' and let me hear it!
What the fuck is a 'surprise'? What the...?
Goddamn it! Shout! Goddamn it!
A surprise! What the hell is a surprise?! The surprise is that in three days, I'll put up 1.8 million for you guys to raid the bandits. But first, kill my legs!
Get it? That's the surprise!
Fatty.
Feifei, the surprise is that in three days, I'll give you 1.8 million taels of silver to leave the city, fight the bandits, and get his leg back.
Big bro, this is a f*cking pleasant surprise! I'm willing to wait for you for three days.
Master Huang, Master Kang is my beloved. You can't take what I love from me!
Help! Help!
[Game sound]